



Nikolaiev Mykhailo Front-End developer

- O Ukraine,Kyiv
- ☑ ab3mn3@gmail.com
- **&** +38-066-800-79-85

SOCIAL

- in/mykhailo-nikolaiev
- ab3MN
- </>
 Codewars

EDUCATION

Thermal power engineer

Kyiv energy college

2006-2010

Thermal power engineer

Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute

2014-2018

SKILLS

- JavaScript
 HTML
- TypeScript
 CSS
- React/Redux Adaptive design
- GIT
- SASS

PROFILE

Courteous and enthusiastic, I am interested in IT. I recently began to be fascinated by web programming, e.g. developing apps and building websites. I am keen to gain more experience in the field. For this reason, I am looking for a company willing to offer me a placement among their developers. In return, I would offer my full commitment, and be a pleasant and friendly addition to your team. I am therefore currently looking for a job or an internship as a front-end developer. My objective is to become a middle within two years.

EXPERIENCE

Main storekeeper

From 2021 to Present | NEXUS ENGINEERING

Storekeeper

From 2018 to 2019 | Kasta

Mechanic of machine shop

From 2014 to 2018 | Kyiv Electric Train Repair Plant

PORTFOLIO

Travel: React/Adeptive Design:

https://nervous-rosalind-6fcc08.netlify.app/

News,posts,movie,weather seacher: React/Redux/TypeScript/AJAX

https://awesome-bose-e43aef.netlify.app/

Authorization:React/Redux/AJAX:

https://jovial-volhard-ca63c1.netlify.app/

CV: Adeptive Design(html,css,js)

https://github.com/ab3MN/mncv.github.io

LANGUAGES

- English
 Ukraine
- Russian